fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Hey... Closet pervert.
Leaf Village Secret Finger Jutsu...
One Thousand Years of Death!
He's totally knocked out...
He's weak, sure enough.
What's with that big frog?
What the hell are you?
Thank you for asking me!
Know me as the Mountain Toad...
spirit sage who acquires immortality,
also commonly called the
Toad Mountain Sage.
Coming Soon!
Enter the
Perverted Sage!
M-Mountain Sage?
Exactly.
Hey... Pervy Sage,
what're you going to do about this?
Here, he was supposed to
watch my training.
You did that to him.
He interfered with my research.
Research?
I'm a writer.
I'm writing a novel.
This is it.
"Make-Out Paradise"
Oh, that is...!
You know this?
I've gotten quite famous.
That's not much of a novel!
In the first place,
what research are you talking about?
You're just peeking at the girls' bath!
— Yikes!
— No!
Idiot, idiot... idiot!
My peeking has been found out.
You pervert.
F-Fool! I'm not just a pervert.
I get inspired by peeking
and can write better pieces.
Liar! No excuses.
More importantly, what're you
going to do about my training?
You mean the walking-on-water technique
you were doing earlier?
You know it?
Then take responsibility
and join my training.
Humph. I don't care about such things.
Hey, hey wait, Pervy Sage!
Join my training, hey!
Shut up! I hate people who
don't know how to talk properly...
And I don't like men.
Oh, umm, umm...
That Make-Out Paradise was
really exciting, cool and interesting.
The purchase or viewing of that novel is
prohibited for those 18 years or younger...
You liar.
The reviews that I've heard are great.
It's useless to flatter me.
I'm a sage!
I'm not the type of fool who can
be coaxed by a fledgling like you.
Oh, hey... wait!
Farewell, kid.
Wow! He's cool even
though he's a pervert.
Hey, Pervy Sage!
Where'd he go?
What're you doing,
you old pervert?
No, no, I'm sorry, Miss
but what lovely breasts...
Pervert!
This grown-up is disgraceful.
Maybe there's nothing special about him,
after all.
But there's nobody else.
Good grief...
As usual, the women in
this village are strong-minded.
However, that's makes them so good.
"As usual"?
Meaning you've come here before?
You.
And you did nothing but peeping, right...?
You Pervy Sage!
Don't say pervert, pervert
in such a loud voice.
Shut up!
So I bet that one shot on
the closet pervert was a fluke...
Anyway, I'll have you take responsibility
for ruining my training! Whoa...
Jeez, you're a noisy brat.
Hey!
Be quiet inside here for awhile.
Hey! Let me out, you jerk!
I want to have a romantic encounter
with a stacked girl.
How dare you do that to me earlier!
Substitution Jutsu.
Sure enough,
he's not an ordinary old man.
Humph! That punk...
It's a million years too soon
for that kid to take me on.
Not really.
It seems you have a bit of talent.
Then you'll watch my training?
Give and take!
I'm not averse to listening
to your favor
as long as you listen to mine.
So which is it?
Listen up...
Nice ripe fruit that looks like this,
like this and this.
I'll watch your training
if you bring me that.
You really will, right?
This Toad Mountain Sage doesn't lie.
Okay, wait!
Plans are plans.
They don't necessarily have to happen...
Hello there, you ladies!
Oh my... You're funny, old man.
No-no, this is the solemn truth.
Yeah, and then,
what happened then?
Hey, Pervy Sage!
Oh no! Pervy Sage, he said.
You fool! Who's a Pervy Sage?
I brought the promised item.
Nice ripe fruit..
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot!
That's not IT!
Looks good!
Don't hesitate. Help yourself.
Thanks.
No!
Where'd the ladies go?!
I got my fill...
Ladies...
No doubt about it. That person is...
Good grief. I've wasted time...
Hold it! Where are you going?!
What about my training?!
I don't care! My precious research
has been ruined thanks to you.
Research, my butt!
I can't be standing around here, either!
I'm going to train hard,
become stronger than anybody,
pass the Chunin exam,
and then I'll exceed the Hokage!
Humph! I don't care about such things.
Here all you do is get in my way...
Jeez, what a repugnant brat!
Stacked girls like the ones
from earlier
are indispensable for
my great writing enterprises!
I see... So I should bring
some stacked girls, right?
Okay.
W-Wow...!
If you gaze at me like that...
I feel embarrassed.
Oh...!
What a...
What a cute girl.
I like you!
You pass!
Idiot.
You're really my type of girl.
What's that technique called?
It's called Sexy Jutsu.
Oh, what an idea. You're a genius.
I get the feeling all adults are
really affected by this technique.
Then you'll watch my training?
Sure! However, I have a condition.
A condition...? What is it?
A-Always be... in that form
when you're in front of me!
Hey! Sure enough,
you're just a pervert! You Pervy Sage!
No! I'm not just a pervert!
As if you didn't know!
I'm a super pervert!
Damn it... He's gone defiant...
Well, brushing off the stuff until
now is a joke,
I'll watch your training.
You mean it, right?
A sage doesn't go back on his word.
Okay, kid.
Do that training that you were
doing before one more time.
Okay!
Okay.
Damn it.
Totally worthless.
Shut up!
It's pointless to wear clothes.
Hey, build up your Chakra
one more time.
One more time?
Just do it, quick.
You!
What?
You're pretty sexy when
you're naked.
Jeez. I'm concentrating,
so don't interfere.
Oh, sorry, sorry. Continue.
You're messing with my focus.
I see... So this is The Seal Formula.
Two Tetragram Seals
making a Double Tetragram Seal...
Is this an 8-Signed Seal Formula?
Nine-Tailed Chakra is leaking
from between the Tetragram Seals...
and is fixed so that it
can return to this kid's Chakra.
Fourth Hokage...
It's to protect this kid, huh?
But after that, it's stopped
with a Five-Pronged Seal...
Putting Odd-Numbered Seal
over Even-Number Seals...
This kid's Chakra and that of
the Nine-Tailed are discreetly intermingled
and are not stable.
No wonder he is not able to
build up Chakra very well.
That tickles... old man.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Perhaps someone else... did it...
The formula is rough.
Well, it's probably Orochimaru.
Kid, give me a hurrah.
What?
Just hurrah. Come on, hurrah.
Jeez, he's demanding.
Five-Pronged Seal... Release!
What're you doing?!
Well, I just pushed
the pressure points for relaxing.
Just try walking on
the water once more...
Sheesh!
What?
I don't know why, but it's going well!
Yahoo!
I guess it's about time to teach him
how to control the Nine-Tailed Chakra.
Okay, kid. Come on out.
I'll teach you an ace technique.
What, what ace technique?
A deadly technique?
There's something you need to
understand well
before I teach you techniques.
You probably haven't noticed,
but you possess two types of Chakra.
Huh? Two types?
Until now, have you ever
felt a special Chakra?
Special? Hmm...
Come to think of it...
Come to think of it,
I get the feeling there were times when...
Chakra suddenly sprang up
and an awesome power came out.
But... I don't really remember those moments.
I see.
But I do remember sensing that
it was different
from the Chakra I always build up.
If I liken it to colors,
while it's always blue...
it felt like it was red or something.
I see.
Okay. That's it for today's training.
What?! Already?
What happened to the ace technique?
I can still train.
With training, a watched pot never boils.
As long as we're here,
let's have a bath...
Not just falling in...
Warms me up.
A drink after training's the best.
Hey, hey, Pervy Sage.
What kind of technique is
that ace technique?
You'll find out tomorrow.
Miser!
We'll turn into boiled frogs if
we stay in here too long.
Ebisu, sorry for snatching
your student.
It's okay. More importantly,
I was surprised...
The Hokage has had us searching
all over for you
and we could never determine
your whereabouts.
To think you were in this village...
The Hokage will be pleased.
Did you tell the Third Hokage about me?
Not yet.
I see. That's for the best.
Sure enough, something
about Orochimaru?
No, unfortunately not.
What?
I just stopped by looking
for material for my novel...
My nature is not to get myself
involved in trouble.
What are you saying?!
You should know!
What is necessary to stop Orochimaru,
known as one of the Sannin,
the legendary three Shinobi,
is the power of another Sannin!
Your power, Jiraiya-sama!
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
First, I need to sign this contract
in blood
and mark it with the fingerprints
of one hand.
Then I build up my Chakra.
The Hand Signs are
Dog, Boar, Bird, Monkey, Sheep.
Then I must place my contract hand
on the place where I want to summon it!
How's that?!
Next time:
"Taught Directly from the Perverted Hermit. It's the Summoning Technique!!"
What is this?!